malaysiakini.tv 2007-10-24

# Welcome to Malaysiakini.tv

**Privacy Policy** Malaysiakini.com is committed to protecting the privacy of all our readers. The following outlines our privacy and data protection policy.

**Collection and Use of User Details** We respect your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us on our web site. Therefore, all personal information collected when you register, subscribe or use the Malaysiakini.com web site will remain within Mkini Dotcom Sdn. Bhd (parent company of Malaysiakini.com) or fully owned subsidiaries of Mkini Dotcom. Your information will not be distributed or sold to third parties. Personal information includes your name, e-mail address, age, gender, income bracket, address, billing information, click-through activity, and any other personal information you may provide us via our web site. When working with any Malaysiakini.com business partner(s) to provide you with additional services and information, your personal information will remain within Mkini Dotcom and will not be revealed to the outside parties.

**Traffic Data** Each time you visit the Malaysiakini.com web site, our servers - like most on the Web - collect some basic technical information such as your browser or platform type, as well as the address of the last URL you visited prior to clicking through to the Malaysiakini.com web site. We also count, track and aggregate your activity into our analysis of general traffic flow at our site (e.g. tracking where the traffic comes from, how the traffic flows in the Malaysiakini.com web site, etc.). This data will be merged into group data and the results of all such research and analysis will be presented as anonymous or aggregated information and will not reveal any personal facts about individual customers. Thus, the aggregated data does not contain anything that can identify you individually. The aggregated information is used to: Improve our understanding of readers' needs when developing the Malaysiakini.com web site Manage our relationship with advertisers Build marketing profile Letters to the Editor We do not retain personal information provided by senders of Letters to the Editor, nor do we trade, sell or otherwise disclose it to third parties.

**Security Policy**

We have appropriate security in place to ensure that your personal details are not misused, accidentally destroyed, lost or altered within our server environment. Other disclosure of personal information. We will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except: (a) as described in this privacy policy, or (b) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority. Policy Change We may make changes to our privacy policy from time to time. It is your responsibility to re-read the Privacy Policy from time to time.

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you can contact:

Mkini Dotcom Sdn. Bhd.  
Malaysiakini.com  
48, Jalan Kemuja,  
Bangsar Utama.  
59000Kuala Lumpur,  
Malaysia.
